insightssuccess.com 2019-04-03

# Insights Success - Privacy Policy - Insightssuccess.com

Insights Success Media Tech LLC owns and operate insightssuccess.com. You may contact us at [editor@insightssuccess.com](mailto:editor@insightssuccess.com)  directly if you have any questions regarding the content and material on the Website or if you have any questions about our privacy policies.

We provide various information, education, technology, healthcare, interviews feature as part of the website. To operate these features, we collect certain non-personal and personal information from our visitors for specific purposes. We may retain personal information for an indefinite amount of time to preserve our database and to comply with various federal and state laws.

We use a third-party advertising company to serve ads on the Website. This advertising company may collect and use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to our site and other websites not owned and operated by Insights Success.

**Refund Policy:**

Insights Success will not accept any cancellations. All payments are to be made in favour Insights Success Media Tech LLC. Rate and changes are subject to change without any notice. Insights Success obligation shall not exceed a refund of amount paid to Insights Success for Advertisement(s).

**Notification of changes:**

We will review our security measures and Privacy Policy on a periodic basis, and we may modify our policies as Insights Success appropriate. We may also change or update our Privacy Policy if we add new services or features and will post these changes
